<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brand Identity on AOE Studios - Advertising Agency in Gothenburg</title>
    <link>https://aoe.studio/tags/brand-identity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brand Identity on AOE Studios - Advertising Agency in Gothenburg</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://aoe.studio/tags/brand-identity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vesta Arkitekter</title>
      <link>https://aoe.studio/work/vesta-arkitekter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aoe.studio/work/vesta-arkitekter/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div id=&#34;context-block&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;context-block_inner&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Vesta Arkitekter is a tactile and thoughtful architecture studio rooted in the traditions of building preservation, material honesty and human-scale design. Working across restoration, new construction and interior architecture, Vesta’s practice bridges the past and the present with quiet precision.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AOE developed the visual identity, templates and brand tools for Vesta Arkitekter, crafting a system that balances the gravitas of historic preservation with the studio’s contemporary sensibilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Named after the Roman goddess of hearth and home, “Vesta” signals care, permanence and the lived experience of space. The brand centers on a material-first philosophy, where wood, stone and brick are not references but starting points.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FourTwoSix Media</title>
      <link>https://aoe.studio/work/fourtwosix-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aoe.studio/work/fourtwosix-media/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div id=&#34;context-block&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;context-block_inner&#34;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;FourTwoSix is a visual production studio that focuses on photorealistic CGI, high-end drone footage, and immersive content, the studio brings narrative and visual precision to everything from social campaigns to branded shorts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Its existing identity no longer reflected the quality and ambition of its work. Despite producing content that consistently outperformed expectations, the brand lacked a cohesive system that could communicate its attention to detail, technical expertise, and sense of storytelling. FourTwoSix needed an identity that felt as intentional and crafted as the work it puts on screen.!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
